(Amy:)I don't know
what you're talking about.
(Penny:)Fine. I'm calling home,
(Penny:)but when I'm done,
you're calling your mother.
(Amy:)Easy for you to say.
(Amy:)You never had to watch
60 Minutes like this.
(Penny:)Hey, Daddy.
(Penny's Dad:)Hey, slugger.
(Penny's Dad:)How's my girl?
(Penny:)Uh, good. Is Mom around?
(Penny's Dad:)Ah, she took your brother out
to celebrate.
(Penny's Dad:)He just got his tenth
one-month sober chip.
(Penny's Dad:)Yeah, she's gonna make him
a little necklace.
(Penny:)Okay, I'll talk to her later.
(Penny:)Uh, Dad, there's something
I need to tell you.
(Penny:)Leonard and I got married.
(Penny's Dad:)You did?
(Penny's Dad:)When?
(Penny:)Last week. I'm sorry,
I should've told you.
(Penny:)It was a spur
of the moment thing.
(Penny:)I feel terrible.
(Penny:)Please don't be
too disappointed.
(Penny's Dad:)Are you happy?
(Howard:)Very.
(Penny:)Leonard is so great.
(Penny's Dad:)Well, then I'm happy for you.
(Penny:)Aw, thank you, Daddy.
(Penny:)That means so much.
(Penny's Dad:)Well, I understand it's hard
(Penny's Dad:)to tell someone something
(Penny's Dad:)if you think
it's gonna upset 'em.
(Penny:)It is.